Yes, I did. Um, and it was everything
they did last year. I mean, if it wasn't
for injuries, um, we'll be talking a
whole different story right now. Um,
they was they were very close. Um, and I
felt like that I definitely could come
in and bring them over the hump.
>> Jake,
>> mute.
>> You can go ahead, James.
>> My bad. Um, one quick followup. What do
you think you can bring to this team
from a defensive standpoint?
>> Uh, energy. Um, just being a vet in this
league for eight years. Um, being with
some great guys, being with some great
defensive ends that I played with. Um,
yeah, great legendary guys that I played
with. And everything that I learned from
them, um, I can teach to the young guys
and to the older guys as well.
>> Jake,
>> hey Ardan, welcome to Indie.
>> How you doing, Jake?
>> Yeah. So, you've been in the AFC South
for a while now. kind of it looks like
you're going on on tour with them, but
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Seeing this team from afar for you know,
you're playing them twice a year.
>> What's your perception of them from like
an opponent and then now seeing like
Louis Anarumo's defense? How do you
think you can fit into that?
>> Well, since I'm on the defensive side, I
paid more attention to close offensive
side and
>> every time we had to play against them,
it was u one of those old school type
football games. one of those they're
going to run it down your throat and if
they continue if they can and they know
they can run it, they're going to
continue to run it. Um, and if you guys
want to pass rush, you have to earn the
right to pass rush going against Indie.
Um, you have to put them in second and
long, third and long. You got to put
them behind the sticks. Um, all those
things. But it was it was coming against
Indie, you had to stop that run. And if
you didn't stop the run, you had a long
day. And I had a long day playing
against Indie.
>> [laughter]
>> It happens. What What uh when you see
Louis Rumo's defense, though, it's it's
kind of a versatile thing, especially
you see defensive ends dropping into
coverage a lot and stuff. What What do
you How do you think you fit into that?
>> Oh, I love it. I love it. Um I've been
studying his defense in Cincinnati. Um I
played against that defense. Um when I
was in San Fran, I saw a lot of things
that he do with the defense with you
never know who's going to be rushing. I
have a guy come up and you think he's
rushing. He's dropping out of there. Um,
he's he he's a great defensive mind mind
coach.
>> Joel,
>> how would you describe your style as a
pass rusher? Ardan
>> pass rusher. Um,
uh, a jack of all trades really because
I I always see and say finesse. I
finesse. I finesse, but I do have a lot
of power in my game. Um, and I power I
power a lot in the beginning and then
start off with the finesse moves and
things of that sort. So that's what I
that's how I would describe myself as
pass rusher.
>> Stephen.
>> Yeah. Hey Ardan. Um, so I mean there are
some there's some young guys on this def
on this defensive line, but also some
vets. I guess a mixture. I mean um do
you feel like there's a leadership role
that you can that you can play as well?
>> Oh, for sure. Um, yeah. year eight going
on year nine. Um definitely a leadership
role. Um but I'm just coming in being
me. I'm coming in being the the guy that
I am, the energy guy. Um I'm I'm a
positive guy. Um I'm just coming in
doing what I do, but also teaching the
younger guys. You know, if the young
guys ask me anything, what question,
whatever they ask me, I'm going to have
an answer to them. And if I don't, then
I'm going send them to the d direction
to get that answer. Um, I have a lot of
um, resources in this league as far as
defensive line that's playing right now
to call him and hey, how would you do
this set? How would you rush this set?
How would you do X, Y, and Z? So, if I
don't know it, then I'll definitely find
out the answer to get back to him
>> and then we'll do our last question from
Joel.
>> What a what do you think was the key for
you kind of finding your place in the
NFL? Because your first couple years
kind of bounced around couple teams,
that kind of thing. What do you think
was your key?
>> Oh, maturing. That's all it was. Um,
just maturing. Um, if you if you looked
at the history of my numbers, the first
three years with the Raiders or just my
whole time with the Raiders, it was ah,
it was nasty. It was like, what are you
doing? Why are you even in the NFL? Um,
but as I as I said, I had to mature,
grow up, and learn that learn how to be
a professional. Um, learning there's a
time and place when to do the fun stuff.
Um, but at the end of the day, you you
are an NFL player and your job is to go
out there and perform the best that you
can on Sunday. And if you can't, then
they'll find somebody else. And luckily,
me getting released from the Raiders had
woke me up to, okay, you need to do you
need to mature and be a uh be a pro in
this league.
>> We'll actually do one more before
wrapping. James, go ahead. I like to ask
guys this because I don't want to take
it for granted, but you know, you've
been at this for a while. It's a hard
league to earn another contract. Have
you had a moment to reflect and kind of
just appreciate everything you went
through from, you know, Georgia as a kid
till now as a grown man?
>> Oh yeah, definitely. Definitely. Um go
back. I do that not even with the
contract. I do that at the end of every
year just looking back how I can get
better, what I've done throughout the
year. Um, just these past couple years
I've been in the in the process of
learning a lot. Um, some things that I
didn't know going into the before that.
Um, but now going through that, it's a
lot of stuff I know now. And if the
younger kids ask for something, then I
can definitely get them um a answer to
the mental side of